# **ANGGI SATRIA**

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER | MOBILE DEVELOPER

Jalan Pupan Rt 009/008 No 32D Pondok Pinang Kby Lama Jakarta Selatan | anggisatria109@gmail.com | +62 895600414111 | https://github.com/AnggiSatria

#### **SUMMARY**

I worked as Front end Developer in startup company, i've learn React Js as library and also use Next Js for framework and then Tailwind CSS for slicing HTML from Figma. I have completely my bootcamp class as Fullstack Developer in Dumbways.id, and also have a portfolio in my github.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Next Js Node Js, Express Js Axios, Socket.IO Tailwind CSS, AntDesign, MUI, Git & Github, MySQL, PostgresSQL

HTML5, CSS, Javascript React Js, MongoDB ,Sequelize, Json Web Token, Bcrpyt, multer, JOI, Redux Toolkit, Redux Thunk, Midtrans, DFD, ERD, UML, Flowcharts, Frontend SEO, React Native, Tanstack Query

SSR, CSR, ISR, Typescript, Java, PHP, Laravel, Shadon/UI, Monolith Server, Hosting Apps with Vercel

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Next JS Developer as Frontend Developer, PT Astra International, Sigmatech November 2024 - Present

- Revision bug
- Handling LCP, FCP & TBT
- Handling SEO up to 100%
- Handling Best practices scale up to 90%
- Slicing UI Emergency Road Assistance
- Slicing UI OSP Project Platform
- · Integration data OSP Project Platform
- · Running sprint from Jira

#### Frontend Developer, PT Alpha Arjuna International

- Develop New User-facing Features
- Write Reusable Code And Libraries
- Enhance Application For Maximum Speed And Scalability

# Feb 2021 - Oct 2022

- Validate Input Before Submitting It To Backend
- Collaborate With Team Members And Stakeholders
- Bridge The Gap Between Graphic Design And **Technical Implementation**

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Informatics Engineering**

Tanri Abeng University

- Oracle Academy: Java Fundamental, Database MySQL
- · Discrete Mathematics, Database Design, Al, Mobile Programming, Web Programming, Data Mining, etc

#### **Bachelor of Informatics Engineering**

Aug 2018 - Dec 2020

Feb 2024 - Present

**Engineering University** 

 Discrete Mathematics, Database Design, Al, Mobile Programming, Web Programming, Data Mining, Calculus, Physics, Aljabar Linear, Algoritma, Java OOP, etc

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: English, Bahasa Indonesia.
- Certifications: Java Fundamental(Oracle), Database Programming(Oracle), Bootcamp Fullstack Class(Dumbways.ID)
- Awards/Activities: Hackathon 2th Position at Dumbways.ID